Investing 

[

Invest

Investment account](https://www.acorns.com/invest)[

Later

Retirement](https://www.acorns.com/later)[

Early Invest

Invest for kids](https://www.acorns.com/early-invest/)[

Sustainable

Sustainable ESG portfolios](https://www.acorns.com/esg-investing)[

Bits of Bitcoin

Bitcoin ETF](https://www.acorns.com/bitcoin-etf/)

Investing  

[Invest

Investment account](https://www.acorns.com/invest)[Later

Retirement](https://www.acorns.com/later)[Early Invest

Invest for kids](https://www.acorns.com/early-invest/)[Sustainable

Sustainable ESG portfolios](https://www.acorns.com/esg-investing)[Bits of Bitcoin

Bitcoin ETF](https://www.acorns.com/bitcoin-etf/)

* * *

The Fine Print of Acorns
------------------------

* [Audited Statement of Financial Condition as of December 31, 2023](https://sqy7rm.media.zestyio.com/Acorns-Securities-SOFC-12-2023-WEBSITE.pdf)
* [Privacy Policy
    ==============](https://www.acorns.com/privacy/)
* [Unaudited Statement of Financial Condition as of June 30, 2024](https://sqy7rm.media.zestyio.com/Acorns-Securities-LLC-Unaudited-Financials-06-30-24.pdf)

ACORNS PRIVACY NOTICE

Effective as of August 14, 2024. 

|     |     |
| --- | --- |
| **FACTS** | **WHAT DOES ACORNS DO WITH YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION?** |
| Why? | Financial companies choose how they share your personal information. Federal law gives consumers the right to limit some but not all sharing. Federal law also requires us to tell you how we collect, share, and protect your personal information. Please read this notice carefully to understand what we do. |
| What? | The types of personal information we collect and share depend on the product or service you have with us. This information can include:<br><br>* Social Security number and account balances<br>* Transaction history and income<br>* Account transactions and checking account information<br><br>When you are no longer our customer, we continue to share your information as described in this notice. |
| How? | All financial companies need to share customers’ personal information to run their everyday business. In the section below, we list the reasons financial companies can share their customers’ personal information; the reasons Acorns chooses to share; and whether you can limit this sharing. |

|     |     |     |
| --- | --- | --- |
| **Reasons we can share your personal information** | **Does Acorns share?** | **Can you limit this sharing?** |
| For our everyday business purposes — such as to process your transactions, maintain your account(s), respond to court orders and legal investigations, or report to credit bureaus | Yes | No  |
| For our marketing purposes — to offer our products and services to you | Yes | No  |
| For joint marketing with other financial companies | No  | We don’t share |
| For our affiliates’ everyday business purposes — information about your transactions and experiences | Yes | No  |
| For our affiliates’ everyday business purposes — information about your creditworthiness | No  | We don’t share |
| For our affiliates to market to you | Yes | Yes |
| For nonaffiliates to market to you | No  | We don’t share |

|     |     |
| --- | --- |
| To limit our sharing | Call the applicable toll-free number below:<br><br>• **Acorns:** [855.604.5130](tel:855.604.5130)<br><br>**Please note:**<br><br>If you are a new customer, we can begin sharing your information 30 days from the date we sent this notice. When you are no longer our customer, we continue to share your information as described in this notice. However, you can contact us at any time to limit our sharing. |
| Questions? | Call 855.604.5130 or go to [https://www.acorns.com/support/contact/](https://www.acorns.com/support/contact/) |

|     |     |
| --- | --- |
| **Who we are** |     |
| Who is providing this notice? | This privacy notice is provided by Acorns Advisers, LLC, Acorns Securities, LLC, Acorns Pay, LLC, and Acorns Grow Incorporated. |

|     |     |
| --- | --- |
| **What we do** |     |
| How does Acorns protect my personal information? | To protect your personal information from unauthorized access and use, we use security measures that comply with federal law. These measures include computer safeguards and secured files and buildings. |
| How does Acorns collect my personal information? | We collect your personal information, for example, when you:<br><br>* Pay your bills or make deposits or withdrawals from your account;<br>* Provide account information or give us your contact information;<br>* Show your government issued ID.<br><br>We also collect your personal information from other companies. |
| Why can’t I limit all sharing? | Federal law gives you the right to limit some, but not all, sharing related to:<br><br>* sharing for affiliates’ everyday business purposes — information about your creditworthiness<br>* affiliates from using your information to market to you<br>* nonaffiliates to market to you<br><br>State laws and individual companies may give you additional rights to limit sharing. See below for more information on your rights under state law. |

|     |     |
| --- | --- |
| **Definitions** |     |
| Affiliates | Companies related by common ownership or control. They can be financial and nonfinancial companies.<br><br>Acorns’ affiliates include Acorns Grow Incorporated, Acorns Advisers, LLC, Acorns Securities, LLC, Acorns Pay, LLC and their respective affiliates |
| Nonaffiliates | Companies not related by common ownership or control. They can be financial and nonfinancial companies.<br><br>* Nonaffiliates we share with can include direct marketing companies. |
| Joint Marketing | A formal agreement between nonaffiliated financial companies that together market financial products or services to you.<br><br>* Our joint marketing partners include financial service companies. |

|     |
| --- |
| **Other important information** |
| California: If your Acorns account has a California mailing address, we will not share personal information we collect about you except to the extent permitted under California law.<br><br>Vermont: If your Acorns account has a Vermont mailing address, we will not share personal information we collect about you with non-affiliates unless the law allows or you provide authorization. |

Acorns Privacy Policy
=====================

Effective as of July 18, 2024.  

Please click [here](https://www.acorns.com/2022-privacy/) to view the previous version of our Privacy Policy.

You can download a printable copy of this Privacy Policy [here](https://www.acorns.com/privacy/). 

This Privacy Policy describes the privacy practices of Acorns Grow Incorporated, Acorns Advisers, LLC, Acorns Securities, LLC, Acorns Pay, LLC and their respective affiliates (collectively, "Acorns," "we", “us” or "our") and how we handle personal information, as defined below, that we collect through our digital properties that link to this Privacy Policy, including our website, mobile application, and browser extensions (collectively, the “Service”), as well as through social media, our marketing activities, our live events and other activities described in this Privacy Policy.

For purposes of this Privacy Policy, “personal information” means information that identifies, relates to, describes, is reasonably capable of being associated with, or could reasonably be linked, directly or indirectly, with a particular consumer or household. Personal information does not include aggregate or deidentified information, or publicly available information lawfully available from governmental records.

If you have registered for an Acorns account or we have otherwise obtained your personal information in connection with providing our financial services, please see our Acorns [Privacy Notice](https://www.acorns.com/privacy/), which applies to our practices subject to certain financial privacy laws. 

**California residents:** See the [California privacy notice](#h_615574473130841672288187278) below for important information about our collection, use and disclosure of your personal information as well as your California privacy rights.

**Nevada residents:** See the [Nevada privacy notice](#h_85683676322881672283985982) below for important information about your Nevada privacy rights.

Index
=====

###   
**Personal information we collect**

Personal information you may provide to us through the Service or otherwise includes:

* Contact data, such as your first and last name, email address, billing and mailing addresses, and phone number.
* Government identifiers, such as national identification number (e.g. Social Security Number, tax identification number, passport number), state or local identification number (e.g., driver’s license or state ID number), and an image of the relevant identification card.
* Profile data, such as the username, account number and password for your Acorns account, date of birth, gender, education, employment details, biographical details, US residency/citizenship status, income, net worth, preferences, investment goals, financial experience, information about your participation in our surveys, and any other information that you add to your account profile.  
* Billing data, such as the payment card or bank account numbers that you use to make payments or transfers through the Service.
* Financial data, such as information about your investment and financial history and interests that you provide through the Service and the information you authorize us to collect from the financial accounts that you connect to the Service.
* Data about others, such as the personal information of any children or others that you provide when opening investment accounts through the Service on their behalf.  We also offer features that help users invite their friends or contacts to use the Service, and we may collect contact details about these invitees so we can deliver their invitations. Please do not refer someone to us or share their contact details with us unless you have their permission to do so. 
* Transactional data, such as information relating to or needed to complete your orders on or through the Service, including transaction history and information about your investments. 
* Communications that we exchange with you, including when you contact us with questions or feedback, through the Service (including our chatbot and other interactive features), social media, survey participation, text messages, or otherwise. 
* Marketing data, such as data you provide when participating in our promotions or in response to our ads or marketing messages.

We may also collect personal information not specifically listed above, which we will use as described in this Privacy Policy or as otherwise disclosed at the time of collection.

Sensitive Personal Information

Some of the personal information described in this Privacy Policy may be considered sensitive under applicable laws.  We do not use sensitive personal information for the purpose of inferring characteristics about you. We will process sensitive personal information only as described in this Privacy Policy and will request your consent to collect or process your sensitive personal information when we legally are required to do so.  

#### **Third-party sources.**

We may combine personal information we receive from you with personal information we obtain from other sources, such as:

* Other financial institutions at which you have an account, such as your bank, credit card issuers and brokerage account providers, when you provide consent for us to collect your information from them.
* Public sources, such as government agencies, public records, social media platforms, and other publicly available sources.
* Data providers, such as information services and data licensors that provide demographic and other information. 
* Our affiliate brand partners, such as the companies that participate in our Acorns Earn program or other promotional programs who share with us information about your use or purchases of their products and services so we can credit your Acorns account with your earned rewards. You can learn more about Acorns Earn here: [https://www.acorns.com/earn/.](https://www.acorns.com/earn/)
* Marketing partners, such as joint marketing partners and event co-sponsors.

#### **Automatic data collection.** 

We, our service providers, and our business partners may automatically log information about you, your computer or mobile device, and your interaction over time with the Service, our communications and other online services, such as:

* Device data, such as your computer’s or mobile device’s operating system type and version, manufacturer and model, browser type, screen resolution, RAM and disk size, CPU usage, device type (e.g., phone, tablet), IP address, unique identifiers (including identifiers used for advertising purposes), language settings, mobile device carrier, radio/network information (e.g., Wi-Fi, Bluetooth, LTE, 3G), and general location information that can be inferred from the foregoing, such as city, state or geographic area.
* Online activity data, such as pages or screens you viewed, how long you spent on a page or screen, the website you visited before browsing to the Service, navigation paths between pages or screens, information about your activity on a page or screen, access times and duration of access, and whether you have opened or forwarded our emails or clicked links within them.
* Precise location data when you authorize the Service to access your device’s location.

#### **Cookies and other technologies.**

The Services employ the following technologies, which facilitate some of the automatic collection described above:

* Cookies, which are files that websites store on a visitor‘s device to uniquely identify the visitor’s browser or to store information or settings in the browser.  The Service employs both session cookies that expire when you close your browser and persistent cookies that remain stored on your device.  Some of the cookies on our services allow third parties like our service providers and advertising partners to collect data needed for the services they provide to us. The Service employs cookies for the following purposes:
    * Technical operation. To allow the technical operation of the Service, such as by remembering your selections and preferences as you navigate the site, and whether you are logged in when you visit password protected areas of the Service.
    * Functionality. To enhance the performance and functionality of our services.
    * Analytics. To help us understand user activity on the Service, including which pages are most and least visited and how visitors move around the Service, as well as user interactions with our emails. 
    * Advertising. To help our third-party advertising partners collect information about how you use the Service and other online services over time, which they use to show you ads on other online services they believe will interest you and measure how the ads perform

You can learn about blocking cookies in the [Your choices](#h_2085486116201672288145071) section below.

* Web beacons, also known as pixel tags or clear GIFs, which are used to demonstrate that a webpage or email address was accessed or opened, or that certain content was viewed or clicked. 
* Local storage technologies, like HTML5, that provide cookie-equivalent functionality but can store larger amounts of data on your device outside of your browser in connection with specific applications.
* Mobile Application Software Development Kits (SDKs).  We may use SDKs in our mobile applications. A SDK is third-party computer code that we or our third party service providers or partners may use for a variety of purposes, including to provide us with analytics regarding the use of our mobile applications, to integrate with social media, add features or functionality to our app, or to facilitate online advertising.
* Chat technologies.  We use chat technologies provided by third-party vendors that employ cookies and software code to operate the chat features you can use to communicate with us through the Service. We and such third-party vendors may monitor, record and use information about webpages visited on our website, your IP address, your general geographic information (e.g., city, state), and other information you share through online chats for the purposes described in this Privacy Policy.

### **How we use your personal information**

We may use your personal information for the following purposes or as otherwise described at the time of collection:

#### **Service delivery.** 

We may use your personal information to:

* provide, operate and improve the Service and our business;
* fulfill your requests for products and services;
* facilitate your invitations to friends who you want to invite to join the Service;
* communicate with you about the Service, including by communicating with you through text messages, chat features, sending announcements, updates, security alerts, money alerts, and support and administrative messages;
* understand your needs and interests, and personalize your experience with the Service and our communications; 
* support our legal or regulatory reporting obligations and risk management procedures (e.g., in relation to anti-money laundering or know your customer (KYC) requirements); and
* troubleshoot and provide support for the Service, and respond to your requests, questions and feedback.

#### **Marketing and advertising.** 

We, our service providers and our third-party advertising partners may collect and use your personal information for marketing and advertising purposes:

* Direct marketing. We may send you direct marketing communications, including through text message or email.  You may opt-out of our marketing communications as described in the [Opt-out of marketing](#h_2529689630011672332596809) section below.  
* Interest-based advertising.  We may engage third-party advertising companies that use cookies and other technologies to collect information about your interaction (including the data described in the [automatic data collection](#h_98800104643701672332798019) section above) over time across the Service, our communications and other online services, and use that information to serve online ads that they think will interest you.  This is called interest-based advertising. We may also share users’ contact data with these companies to facilitate interest-based advertising to those or similar users on other online platforms. You can learn more about [your choices](#h_2085486116201672288145071) for limiting interest-based advertising in the [Your choices](#h_2085486116201672288145071) section below.
* Promotions. We use personal information to provide the promotional programs that we offer, such as the rewards we provide to participants in the [Acorns Earn](https://www.acorns.com/earn/) program or to users who refer friends or contacts to Acorns. We may provide these programs in collaboration with affiliate brand partners and other businesses, websites, mobile applications or third parties. Each such program will be subject to and governed by our [Terms of Use](https://www.acorns.com/terms/), this Privacy Policy, and any other applicable rules or terms and conditions that we or the relevant third parties may post or make available to you. 

#### **Research and development.** 

We may use your personal information for research and development purposes, including to analyze and improve the Service and our business.  We may process your personal information as well as the personal information of other individuals from whom we collect such information by creating aggregated or deidentified data.  Such aggregated or deidentified data is non-personal information. We may use this aggregated or deidentified data and disclose it to other parties for our lawful business purposes, including to analyze and improve the Service and promote our business.  

#### **Compliance and protection.** 

We may use your personal information to:

* comply with applicable laws, lawful requests, and legal process, such as to respond to subpoenas or requests from government authorities;
* protect our, your or others’ rights, privacy, safety or property (including by making and defending legal claims); 
* audit our internal processes for compliance with legal and contractual requirements or our internal policies; 
* enforce the terms and conditions that govern the Service; and 
* prevent, identify, investigate and deter fraudulent, harmful, unauthorized, unethical or illegal activity, including fraud, cyberattacks and identity theft.

#### **Retention.**

The length of time we retain particular categories of personal information is determined based on whether it is sufficient to fulfill the purposes for which we collected it, including to satisfy legal, regulatory, accounting, or reporting requirements, establish or defend legal claims, enforce our agreements, resolve disputes or fraud prevention, or as otherwise permitted under applicable law.  

### **How we share your personal information**

We may share your personal information with the following parties and as otherwise described in this Privacy Policy or at the time of collection.  

Affiliates.  Our corporate parent, subsidiaries, and affiliates, for purposes consistent with this Privacy Policy.

Service providers.  Service providers that provide services on our behalf or help us operate the Service or our business (such as mail delivery, hosting, information technology, chat feature support, customer support, email delivery, text message delivery, marketing, consumer research, and website analytics). We enter into contracts with our service providers that require them to handle your personal information only as consistent with this Privacy Policy. 

Financial institutions. Acorns uses Plaid Inc. (“Plaid”) to gather your data from financial institutions. By using the Service, you grant Acorns the right, power, and authority to act on your behalf to access and transmit your personal and financial information from your relevant financial institution. You agree to your personal and financial information being transferred, stored, and processed by Plaid. If you choose to apply for an Acorns VisaTM debit card, you understand that such card is issued by Lincoln Savings Bank or nbkc bank.  Acorns also uses financial institutions to process your ACH funds transfers from your funding source bank account to Acorns for use of the Service.  

Gift Recipients and payment processors. If you access Acorns to transfer funds to an Acorns account holder through the Acorns Early Gifting feature, you authorize the sharing of your name, the status of your gift, and the amount of the transfer with the recipient Acorns account holder. Acorns partners with Stripe, a third-party payment processor, to facilitate your gifts. Acorns facilitates such transactions by collecting information from gift contributors necessary to enable the payment processing and submitting it to the processor. Use of this feature is governed by the Early Gifting Terms of Use: [https://www.acorns.com/early-gifting-terms-of-use/.](https://www.acorns.com/early-gifting-terms-of-use/)

Advertising partners.  Third-party advertising companies for the [interest-based advertising purposes](#h_52700337646431672332824426) described above. 

Affiliate brand partners.  When you make a purchase on one of our affiliate brand partner sites, we may share information about you with those affiliate brand partners to operate the relevant promotional program, for example, so that we can credit your account with any earned rewards. 

Third parties designated by you. We may share your personal data with third parties where you have instructed us or provided your consent to do so. For example, we may share your personal information with affiliate brand partners or other third-parties with whom we are collaborating in our promotional programs or to offer you additional services. We will share personal information that is needed for these other companies to make the promotion available, provide the services that you have requested and track participation in the promotion or service. 

Professional advisors.  Professional advisors, such as lawyers, auditors, bankers and insurers, where necessary in the course of the professional services that they render to us.

Authorities and others. Law enforcement, government authorities, and private parties, as we believe in good faith to be necessary or appropriate for the [compliance and protection purposes](#h_39840420551631672332913675) described above. 

Business transferees.  Parties (and their advisors) to business transactions or proposed transactions involving a corporate divestiture, merger, consolidation, acquisition, reorganization, sale or other disposition of all or any portion of the business or assets of, or equity interests in, Acorns or our affiliates (including, in connection with insolvency, bankruptcy or similar proceedings).  

### **Your privacy rights and choices** 

In this section, we describe the rights and choices available to all users. California residents can find additional information about their rights [here](#h_615574473130841672288187278) and Nevada residents can find additional information [here](#h_85683676322881672283985982).

Privacy laws, other than the CCPA, apply to much of the personal information that we collect, use, and disclose. When these other laws apply, personal information may be exempt from, or outside the scope of the privacy rights described below. For example, information subject to certain federal privacy laws, such as the Gramm-Leach-Bliley Act or the Health Insurance Portability and Accountability, is exempt from CCPA rights requests. We therefore may decline all, or part of your request related to exempt personal information. This means that we may not provide some, or all, of this personal information when you make a right to access request. We may also not delete or correct some, or all, personal information when you make a deletion or correction request.

Access or update your information. If you have an Acorns account, you can review and update information in your account settings.

Privacy rights.

Depending on where you live, applicable law may provide you with certain rights regarding your personal information:

* Right to access. You can request a copy of certain personal information that we have collected about you and have it provided in a portable, machine-readable manner.
* Right to deletion. You can request that we delete personal information that we collected from you.
* Right to correction. You can request that we correct inaccurate personal information that we have collected about you.
* Right to opt-out. You can request to opt-out of disclosures of your personal information that constitute “selling” of your personal information as defined in applicable law.

You may submit requests to exercise your right to access, deletion and correction by emailing [support@acorns.com](mailto:support@acorns.com) or writing to Acorns Legal, 5300 California Ave., Irvine, CA 92617. The rights described above are not absolute, and in certain cases, we may decline your request as permitted by law. We cannot process your request if you do not provide us with sufficient detail to allow us to understand and respond to it.

Identity verification. We need to verify your identity to process your requests to exercise your rights to access, deletion, and correction, and we reserve the right to confirm your entitlement to exercise these rights under the laws in your jurisdiction. To verify your identity, we may require you to log into your Acorns account if you have one, provide identifiers we can match against information we may have collected from you previously, confirm your request using the email address or telephone number used to make the request, provide government identification, or provide a declaration under penalty of perjury, where permitted by law.  

#### Opt-out of marketing communications. 

You may opt-out of marketing-related emails by following the opt-out or unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of the email, or by [contacting us](#h_996856840129341672288181881).  Please note that if you choose to opt-out of marketing-related emails, you may continue to receive service-related and other non-marketing emails.  

If you receive text messages from us, you may opt out of receiving further text messages from us by replying STOP.   

#### Mobile location data.  

If you have previously opted into sharing your device’s precise geolocation information, you can opt-out in your mobile device’s settings.  

#### Cookies. 

Most browsers let you remove or reject cookies.  To do this, follow the instructions in your browser settings.  Many browsers accept cookies by default until you change your settings.  Please note that if you set your browser to disable cookies, our websites may not work properly. For more information about cookies, including how to see what cookies have been set on your device and how to manage and delete them, visit [www.allaboutcookies.org](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/).  To opt-out of data collection through our analytics provider, Google Analytics, visit [https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout).  

#### Blocking web beacons.

Most browsers offer settings that allow you to configure your device to prevent images that would include web beacons/clear GIFs from loading.  

#### Interest-based advertising. 

Steps you can take to opt-out out of use of your personal information for interest-based advertising include:

* Browser settings.  Blocking third-party cookies in your browser settings.
* Privacy browsers/plug-ins. Using privacy browsers or ad-blocking browser plug-ins that let you block tracking technologies. 
* Platform settings. Using Google’s and Facebook’s opt-out tools to opt-out of their use of your information for interest-based advertising:
    * Google: [https://adssettings.google.com/](https://adssettings.google.com/)
    * Facebook: [https://www.facebook.com/about/ads](https://www.facebook.com/about/ads) 
* Ad industry tools.  Opting out of interest-based ads from companies participating in the following industry opt-out programs: 
    * Network Advertising Initiative: [http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt\_out.asp](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp)
    * Digital Advertising Alliance: optout.aboutads.info.
    * AppChoices mobile app, available at [https://www.youradchoices.com/appchoices](https://www.youradchoices.com/appchoices), which will allow you to opt-out of interest-based ads in mobile apps served by participating members of the Digital Advertising Alliance. 
* Mobile settings.  Using your mobile device settings to limit use of the advertising ID associated with your mobile device for [interest-based advertising purposes](#h_52700337646431672332824426).

You will need to apply these opt-out settings on each device and browser from which you wish to opt-out.  Please note that we also may work with companies that offer their own opt-out mechanisms and may not participate in the ad industry opt-out mechanisms that we linked to above.   

#### Do not track. 

Some Internet browsers may be configured to send “Do Not Track” signals to the online services that you visit.  We currently do not respond to “Do Not Track” or similar signals except where we expressly indicate otherwise.  To find out more about “Do Not Track,” please visit [http://www.allaboutdnt.com](http://www.allaboutdnt.com/).  

#### Declining to provide information.

We need to collect personal information to provide certain services.  If you do not provide the information we identify as required or mandatory, we may not be able to provide those services.  

#### Close your account.

To request that we close your Service account or delete your personal information associated with your account, please [contact us](#h_996856840129341672288181881) to request account closure.  Certain personal information associated with your account may be retained after account closure in accordance with our data retention policies where required or permitted by applicable law.

### **Other sites and services**

The Service may contain links to websites, mobile applications, and other online services operated by third parties.  In addition, our content may be integrated into web pages or other online services that are not associated with us.  These links and integrations are not an endorsement of, or representation that we are affiliated with, any third party.  We do not control websites, mobile applications or online services operated by third parties, and we are not responsible for their actions. We encourage you to read the privacy policies of the other websites and mobile applications and online services you use.  For example, when you navigate to the “Acorns Merch Shop”, you are leaving Acorns.com. The Acorns Merch Shop is hosted by Shopify Inc. and any use of such page is governed by the Shopify privacy policy found at [https://www.shopify.com/legal/privacy.](https://www.shopify.com/legal/privacy.)

### **Security** 

We employ, test and regularly re-evaluate appropriate technical, organizational and physical safeguards designed to protect the confidentiality, integrity and security of the personal information we collect, both when we receive it and during transit, such as by encrypting credit card numbers and other sensitive personal information that you enter into the Service.  However, security risk is inherent in all internet and information technologies and we cannot guarantee the security of your personal information. 

### **International data transfer**

We are headquartered in the United States and may use service providers that operate in other countries. Your personal information may be transferred to the United States or other locations where privacy laws may not be as protective as those in your state, province, or country.  

### **Children**  

The Service is not intended for use by children under 18 years of age. If we learn that we have collected personal information through the Service from a child under 18 in a manner prohibited by law, we will comply with legal requirements to delete it. We encourage parents or guardians with concerns to contact us. 

### **Changes to this Privacy Policy** 

We reserve the right to modify this Privacy Policy at any time. If we make material changes to this Privacy Policy, we will notify you by updating the date of this Privacy Policy and posting it on the Service. If required by law we will also provide notification of changes in another way that we believe is reasonably likely to reach you, such as via email or another manner through the Service.  Any modifications to this Privacy Policy will be effective upon our posting the modified version (or as otherwise indicated at the time of posting). In all cases, your use of the Service after the effective date of any modified Privacy Policy indicates your acceptance of the modified Privacy Policy.

### **How to contact us**

Acorns Grow Incorporated

5300 California Avenue

Irvine, CA 92617

### **California privacy notice**

This notice describes our collection, use and disclosure of personal information of California residents in our capacity as a “business” under the California Consumer Privacy Act (“CCPA”) and their rights with respect to their personal information. For purposes of this California privacy notice, “personal information” has the meaning given in the CCPA but does not include information exempted from the scope of the CCPA, such as information described in our [Acorns Privacy Notice](https://www.acorns.com/privacy/) pursuant to the Gramm-Leach-Bliley Act. 

Your privacy rights. If you’re a California resident, you have the following rights under the CCPA. As required by the CCPA, we compile metrics on California Privacy Rights Reporting that can be found here.

* Right to know. You can request information about the categories of personal information that we have collected; the categories of sources from which we collected personal information; the business or commercial purpose for collecting, sharing and/or selling personal information; the categories of any personal information that we sold or disclosed for a business purpose; and the categories of any third parties with whom personal information was sold, shared or disclosed for a business purpose.
* Right to access. You can request a copy of certain personal information that we have collected about you.
* Right to deletion. You can request that we delete personal information that we collected from you.
* Right to correction. You can request that we correct inaccurate personal information that we have collected about you.
* Right to opt-out. You can request to opt-out of disclosures of your personal information that constitute “selling” or “sharing” of your personal information as defined in the CCPA.
* Nondiscrimination. You are entitled to exercise the rights described above free from discrimination as prohibited by the CCPA.

You may submit requests to exercise your right to know, access, deletion and correction by emailing [support@acorns.com](mailto:support@acorns.com) or writing to Acorns Legal, 5300 California Ave., Irvine, CA 92617. The rights described above are not absolute, and in certain cases, we may decline your request as permitted by law. We cannot process your request if you do not provide us with sufficient detail to allow us to understand and respond to it. 

Identity verification. We need to verify your identity to process your requests to exercise your rights to know, access, deletion, and correction, and we reserve the right to confirm your California residency. To verify your identity, we may require you to log into your Acorns account if you have one, provide identifiers we can match against information we may have collected from you previously, confirm your request using the email address or telephone number used to make the request, provide government identification, or provide a declaration under penalty of perjury, where permitted by law. 

Authorized agents. Your authorized agent may make a request on your behalf upon our verification of the agent’s identity and our receipt of a copy of a valid power of attorney given to your authorized agent pursuant to applicable state law. If you have not provided your agent with such a power of attorney, we may ask you and/or your agent to take additional steps permitted by law to verify that your request is authorized, such as information required to verify your identity and that you have given the authorized agent permission to submit the request. 

Information practices. The following describes our practices currently and during the past 12 months:

* Sales and sharing of personal information. Our use of the [interest-based advertising](#h_92485476370681672333159212) services described above may constitute “sharing” of your personal information under the CCPA from which you have the right to opt-out. That is because these services use our users’ personal information (specifically, the contact data, device data and online activity data described above in [Personal information we collect](#h_104698683103101672288118177)) to show you ads they think may interest you on other online services. You may opt-out of such sharing by Acorns by clicking ‘Your Privacy Choices’ at the footer of this site. Your request to opt-out will apply only to the browser and the device from which you submit the request. We do not “sell” personal information as defined by the CCPA, and have no actual knowledge that we have sold or shared the personal information of California residents under 16 years of age.
* Sensitive personal information. We do not use or disclose sensitive personal information for purposes that California residents have a right to limit under the CCPA.
* Deidentified data. We do not to attempt to reidentify deidentified information that we derive from personal information, except for the purpose of testing whether our deidentification processes comply with applicable law.
* Sources and purposes. We collect all categories of personal information from [the sources](#h_104698683103101672288118177) and use them for the business/commercial [purposes](#h_856038788108651672288126919) described above in the Privacy Policy. 
* Collection and disclosure. The chart below describes the personal information we collect by reference to the categories of personal information specified in the CCPA (Cal. Civ. Code §1798.140), and the categories of third parties to whom we disclose it. The terms in the chart refer to the categories of information and third parties detailed above in the [Personal information we collect](#h_104698683103101672288118177) section. Information you voluntarily provide to us, such as in free-form webforms, may contain other categories of personal information not described below. We may also disclose personal information to professional advisors, law enforcement and government authorities, and business transferees as described above in the [How we share your personal information](#h_818195845113851672288137822) section of this Privacy Policy. 

|     |     |
| --- | --- |
| **Statutory category  <br>Personal information we collect** | **Categories of third parties to whom we disclose the personal information for a business purpose** |
| Identifiers<br><br>Contact data<br><br>Communications data<br><br>Marketing data<br><br>Device data | Affiliates <br><br>Service providers<br><br>Advertising partners |
| California Customer Records  <br>(as defined in Cal. Civ. Code §1798.80)<br><br>Contact data<br><br>Communications data<br><br>Marketing data<br><br>Device data | Affiliates <br><br>Service providers<br><br>Advertising partners |
| Commercial Information<br><br>Contact data<br><br>Online activity data<br><br>Marketing data | Affiliates <br><br>Service providers<br><br>Advertising partners |
| Internet or Network Information <br><br>Device data<br><br>Online activity data | Affiliates <br><br>Service providers<br><br>Advertising partners |
| Geolocation data<br><br>Device data (e.g., city, state derived from IP address) | Affiliates <br><br>Service providers |
| Inferences<br><br>May be derived from any of the above categories | Affiliates <br><br>Service providers<br><br>Advertising partners |
| Sensitive Personal Information<br><br>Government identifiers, such as Social security, driver’s license, state identification card, or passport number<br><br>Citizenship or immigration status<br><br>Precise geolocation | Affiliates<br><br>Service providers |

### **Nevada privacy notice**

Certain Nevada consumers may opt out of the sale of “personally identifiable information” for “monetary consideration,” as defined under Nevada law, to a person for that person to license or sell such information to others. We do not engage in such activity; however, if you are a Nevada resident who has purchased goods or services from us, you may submit a request to opt out of any future sales under Nevada law by contacting us as detailed in the “Contact Us” section above. Please note we may take reasonable steps to verify your identity and the authenticity of the request.

#### Have any questions?

###### Products

###### Who we are

###### Why start now

**Investment products | Not FDIC insured | No bank guarantee | May lose value**  
  
**Important Disclosures**

**Paid advertisement.** Dwayne Johnson is an investor in Acorns Grow Incorporated, is a director of its affiliate Acorns Labs, is an Acorns customer, and together with his creative agency receives substantial compensation from Acorns and its affiliates to promote Acorns and therefore has a conflict of interest that can be expected to bias his views. Statements are not necessarily representative of the experience or views of other customers and are not guarantees of performance or success. Nothing here should be viewed as an endorsement or testimonial regarding Acorns Advisers LLC's investment advisory services. Acorns is not a bank. Acorns Visa™ debit cards and banking services are issued and provided by Lincoln Savings Bank or nbkc bank, Members FDIC, to Acorns Checking account holders that are U.S. residents over the age of eighteen (18).  
**Investing involves risk, including loss of principal.** Please consider, among other important factors, your investment objectives, risk tolerance and Acorns’ pricing before investing. Investment advisory services offered by Acorns Advisers, LLC (Acorns), an SEC-registered investment advisor. Brokerage services are provided to clients of Acorns by Acorns Securities, LLC, an SEC-registered broker-dealer and member [FINRA](https://www.finra.org/#/)/[SIPC](https://www.sipc.org/).

1\. **Round-Ups® investments** are transferred from your linked funding source (checking account) to your Acorns Invest account, where the funds are invested into a portfolio of selected ETFs. If you do not maintain an adequate amount of funds in your funding source sufficient to cover your Round-Ups® investment, you could incur overdraft fees with your financial institution. Only purchases made with Round-Up accounts linked to your Acorns account with the feature activated are eligible for the Round- Ups® investment feature. Round-Up investments from your funding source will be processed when your Pending Round-Ups® investments reach or exceed $5.   

2\. **Acorns Checking Real-Time Round-Ups®** invests small amounts of money from purchases made using an Acorns Checking account into the client’s Acorns Investment account. Requires both an active Acorns Checking account and an Acorns Investment account in good standing. Real-Time Round-Ups® investments accrue instantly for investment during the next trading window.

3\. A properly suggested **portfolio recommendation** is dependent upon current and accurate financial and risk profiles. Clients who have experienced changes to their goals, financial circumstances, or investment objectives, or who wish to modify their portfolio recommendation, should promptly update their information in the Acorns app or through the website.

4\. **Acorns Earn** provides subscribers access to shop with our partners and earn bonus investments into your Acorns Invest portfolios when purchasing items from the partner brands. Acorns Earn rewards investments are made by Acorns Grow, Incorporated into your Acorns Invest account through a partnership Acorns Grow maintains with each Acorns Earn partner. Acorns may receive compensation from business partners in connection with certain promotions in which Acorns refers clients to such partners for the purchase of non-investment consumer products or services. This type of marketing partnership gives Acorns an incentive to refer clients to business partners instead of to businesses that are not partners of Acorns. This conflict of interest affects the ability of Acorns to provide clients with unbiased, objective promotions concerning the products and services of its business partners. This could mean that the products and/or services of other businesses, that do not compensate Acorns, may be more appropriate for a client than the products and/or services of Acorns business partners. Subscribers are, however, not required to purchase the products and services Acorns promotes. Amount earned and invested through Acorns Earn since inception as of July 1, 2024.

5\. Acorns **Subscription Fees** are assessed based on the plan of services in which you are enrolled. Acorns does not charge transactional fees, commissions or fees based on assets for accounts under $1 million. Acorns may receive compensation from business partners in connection with certain promotions in which Acorns refers clients to such partners for the purchase of non-investment consumer products or services. This type of marketing partnership gives Acorns an incentive to refer clients to business partners instead of to businesses that are not partners of Acorns. This conflict of interest affects the ability of Acorns to provide clients with unbiased, objective promotions concerning the products and services of its business partners. This could mean that the products and/or services of other businesses, that do not compensate Acorns, may be more appropriate for a client than the products and/or services of Acorns business partners. Subscribers are, however, not required to purchase the products and services Acorns promotes.

6. **Acorns is not a bank.** Acorns Visa™ debit cards and banking services are issued by Lincoln Savings Bank or nbkc bank, members FDIC. Acorns Checking clients are not charged overdraft fees, maintenance fees, or ATM fees for cash withdrawals from in-network ATMs. Please see your Acorns Subscription Center or Account Statements for a description of the fees you pay to Acorns for its services. Any balances you hold with Lincoln Savings Bank or nbkc bank, including but not limited to those balances held in Acorns Checking accounts are added together and are insured up to $250,000 per depositor through Lincoln Savings Bank or nbkc bank, Members FDIC. Acorns Checking is not FDIC-insured. FDIC insurance only covers the failure of an insured bank. If you have funds jointly owned, these funds would be separately insured for up to $250,000 for each joint account owner. Lincoln Savings Bank or nbkc bank utilizes a deposit network service, which means that at any given time, all, none, or a portion of the funds in your Acorns Checking accounts may be placed into and held beneficially in your name at other depository institutions which are insured by the Federal Deposit Insurance Corporation (FDIC). For a complete list of other depository institutions where funds may be placed, please visit [https://www.cambr.com/bank-list](https://www.cambr.com/bank-list). Balances moved to network banks are eligible for FDIC insurance once the funds arrive at a network bank. To learn more about pass-through deposit insurance applicable to your account, please see the Account Documentation. Additional information on FDIC insurance can be found at [https://www.fdic.gov/resources/deposit-insurance/](https://www.fdic.gov/resources/deposit-insurance/).

7. **Early Payday** depends on the timing of the submission of the payment file from the payer and fraud prevention restrictions. Funds are generally available on the day the payment file is received, up to 2 days earlier than the scheduled payment date. Timing may vary. 

8. **The ETFs** comprising the portfolios charge fees and expenses that will reduce a client’s return. Investors should consider the investment objectives, risks, charges and expenses of the funds carefully before investing. Investment policies, management fees and other information can be found in the individual ETF’s prospectus. Please read each prospectus carefully before investing.

9\. **Acorns does not provide access to invest directly in Bitcoin.** Bitcoin exposure is provided through the ETF BITO, which invests in Bitcoin futures. This is considered a high-risk investment given the speculative and volatile nature. Investments in Bitcoin ETFs may not be appropriate for all investors and should only be utilized by those who understand and accept those risks. Investors seeking direct exposure to the price of bitcoin should consider a different investment. 

10\. **The ESG (Environmental, social, and governance) investment strategies** may limit the types and number of investment opportunities available, as a result, the portfolio may underperform others that do not have an ESG focus. Companies selected for inclusion in the portfolio may not exhibit positive or favorable ESG characteristics at all times and may shift into and out of favor depending on market and economic conditions. Environmental criteria considers how a company performs as a steward of nature. Social criteria examine how it manages relationships with employees, suppliers, customers, and the communities where it operates. Governance deals with a company’s leadership, executive pay, audits, internal controls, and shareholder rights.

11\. **Invest,** an individual investment account which invests in a portfolio of ETFs (exchange traded funds) recommended to clients based on their investment objectives, time horizon, and risk tolerance. 

12\. **Later**, an Individual Retirement Account (either Traditional, ROTH or SEP IRA) selected for clients based on their answers to a suitability questionnaire. Please consult your tax advisor with any questions. Existing customers in Acorns Gold or Silver subscription plans can opt into the Acorns Later Match feature and receive either a 3% or 1% IRA match, respectively, on new contributions made to an Acorns Later account. New customers in these subscription plans are automatically eligible for the Later Match feature at the applicable 3% and 1% match rate. All Later funds for both new and existing customers must be held in an Acorns Later account for at least four years to keep the earned IRA match and all or a portion of IRA Match may be subject to recapture by Acorns if customer downgrades to a Subscription Plan with a lower monthly fee.  
  
For informational purposes only. This is solely intended to provide notification of an available product or service. This is not a recommendation to buy, sell, hold, or roll over any asset, adopt an investment strategy, or use a particular account type. This information does not consider the specific investment objectives, tax and financial conditions or particular needs of any specific person. Investors should discuss their specific situation with their financial professional.

13\. **Acorns Early Invest,** an UTMA/UGMA investment account managed by an adult custodian until the minor beneficiary comes of age, at which point they assume control of the account. Money in a custodial account is the property of the minor.  Customers in the Gold Subscription Plan are automatically eligible for a 1% "Early Match" promotion on deposits by the Customer of up to $7,000 a year per Early Account. All funds must be held in the applicable Acorns Early Account for at least four years of the Early Match deposit date or until the beneficiary reaches the applicable Age of Transfer, whichever is earlier. The Early Match will be subject to recapture by Acorns if funds are withdrawn from the Early Account during the four year period, up to the amount for which a 1% Early Match was received. The Early Match will also be subject to recapture if a customer downgrades to a Subscription Plan with a lower monthly fee within this period.

14\. **Custom Portfolios** are non-discretionary investment advisory accounts, managed by the customer. Custom Portfolios are not available as a stand alone account and clients must have an Acorns Invest account. Custom portfolios are not instant trading. Clients wanting more control over order placement and execution may need to consider alternative investment platforms before adding a Custom portfolio account.

15\. The **Acorns Gold GoHenry Benefit** is available only to Acorns subscribers who subscribe to the Acorns Gold Plan and is for the monthly GoHenry Child or Family Plan Membership Fee, subject to these Waiver Terms. You will remain responsible for any other fees that you owe under the GoHenry Cardholder Terms and Conditions that are not included in the monthly GoHenry Child or Family Plan Membership Fee, as applicable.

16\. © GoHenry Inc. ("Acorns Early") All rights reserved. Acorns Early is not a bank. The Acorns Early card is issued by Community Federal Savings Bank, member FDIC, pursuant to license by Mastercard International. Our office is located at Acorns Early, 5300 California Avenue, Irvine, CA 92617. Cardholder Terms and limits apply.

17. **It is not possible to invest directly in an index.** Past performance is no guarantee of future results.  

18\. Acorns reserves the right to restrict or revoke any and all offers at any time.

19\. **Compounding** is the process in which an asset’s earning from either capital gains or interest are reinvested to generate additional earnings over time. It does not ensure positive performance, nor does it protect against loss. Acorns clients may not experience compound returns and investment results will vary based on market volatility and fluctuating prices. 

20\. **Diversification** and asset allocation do not guarantee a profit, nor do they eliminate the risk of loss of principal.

21\. App rating references the combined all-time star rating received in Google Play and Apple App Store. App Store rating as of 5/30/24.

22\. ‘Save and Invest’ refers to a client’s ability to utilize the Acorns Real-Time Round-Ups® investment feature to seamlessly invest small amounts of money from purchases using an Acorns investment account.

23\. The information contained on this website should not considered an offer, solicitation of an offer or advice to buy or sell any security or investment product. The information should not be construed as tax or legal advice. Please consult your tax advisor with any questions.  
  
24\. Comparisons are based on the national average Annual Percentage Yields (APY) published in the FDIC National Rates and Rate Caps as of October 16, 2023.

25\. As of November 8, 2024, Mighty Oak Checking Annual Percentage Yield (APY) is 2.72% and Emergency Fund APY is 4.29%. APY is variable and subject to change at our discretion, without prior notice. No minimum opening deposit or minimum balance required. Acorns is not a bank. Banking services provided by and Mighty Oak Debit Cards issued and provided by nbkc bank, Member FDIC, to Acorns Checking account holders that are U.S. residents over the age of eighteen (18).  

26. On August 21, 2024, Acorns changed the names of its Subscription Plans from "Personal," "Personal Plus," and "Premium" to "Bronze," "Silver," and "Gold." No other changes were made to the Subscription Plans at that time.

27\. Over $22 billion invested since inception as of 6/26/2024. 

28\. Amount invested from Round-Ups alone since inception as of July 31, 2024.   

Acorns, Round-Ups® investments, Real-Time Round-Ups® investments, Invest the Change and the Acorns logo are registered trademarks of Acorns Grow Incorporated. All product and company names are trademarks™ or registered® trademarks of their respective holders. Use of them does not imply any affiliation with or endorsement by them. 

For additional important risks, disclosures, and information, please visit [https://www.acorns.com/terms/](https://www.acorns.com/terms/)

© 2024 Acorns Grow Incorporated | [Disclosures](https://www.acorns.com/disclosures) | [Accessibility](https://www.acorns.com/accessibility)

Acorns

Invest spare change

✕
